let savollar13 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "aboard",
      answer: "B. bortda",
      options: [
        "A. ichida",
        "B. bortda",
        "C. samolyotda",
        "D. bortda"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "bitter",
      answer: "C. achchiqlangan",
      options: [
        "A. ahmoq",
        "B. jahldor",
        "C. achchiqlangan",
        "D. norozi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bullet",
      answer: "A. o'q",
      options: [
        "A. o'q",
        "B. patron",
        "C. gilza",
        "D. snar'yad"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "devil",
      answer: "D. shayton",
      options: [
        "A. iblis",
        "B. jin",
        "C. arvoh",
        "D. shayton"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to drift",
      answer: "B. oqib ketmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ketmoq",
        "B. oqib ketmoq",
        "C. uchmoq",
        "D. siljimoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to enforce",
      answer: "C. joriy qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. buyurmoq",
        "B. ta'kidlamoq",
        "C. joriy qilmoq",
        "D. kuchlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "fountain",
      answer: "A. favvora",
      options: [
        "A. favvora",
        "B. buloq",
        "C. chasma",
        "D. fontan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "harbor",
      answer: "B. port",
      options: [
        "A. bandargoh",
        "B. port",
        "C. ko'rfaz",
        "D. qirg'oq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to inhabit",
      answer: "D. istiqomat qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tik turmoq",
        "B. kelmoq",
        "C. joylashmoq",
        "D. istiqomat qilmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to march",
      answer: "A. marsh qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. marsh qilmoq",
        "B. yurmoq",
        "C. harakatlanmoq",
        "D. chopmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "millionaire",
      answer: "C. millioner",
      options: [
        "A. boyvacha",
        "B. badavlat",
        "C. millioner",
        "D. boy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "port",
      answer: "B. bandargoh",
      options: [
        "A. oromgoh",
        "B. bandargoh",
        "C. pristani",
        "D. ko'rfaz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "sheriff",
      answer: "D. sherif",
      options: [
        "A. politsiyachi",
        "B. qorovul",
        "C. nazorachi",
        "D. sherif"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to startle",
      answer: "C. qo'rqitib yubormoq",
      options: [
        "A. baqirmoq",
        "B. urmoq",
        "C. qo'rqitib yubormoq",
        "D. vahima qimoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to sweat",
      answer: "A. terlаmoq",
      options: [
        "A. terlаmoq",
        "B. namlanmoq",
        "C. ho'llanmoq",
        "D. bug'lanmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "trigger",
      answer: "B. miltiq tepkisi",
      options: [
        "A. kurок",
        "B. miltiq tepkisi",
        "C. richag",
        "D. tugma"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to unify",
      answer: "D. birlashtirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qo'shmoq",
        "B. umumlashtirmoq",
        "C. jamlаmoq",
        "D. birlashtirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "vessel",
      answer: "C. kema",
      options: [
        "A. qayiq",
        "B. kater",
        "C. kema",
        "D. karabl"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "voyage",
      answer: "A. sayohat",
      options: [
        "A. sayohat",
        "B. safar",
        "C. parvoz",
        "D. yo'l"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to worship",
      answer: "B. ibodat qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. topinmoq",
        "B. ibodat qilmoq",
        "C. egilmoq",
        "D. e'zozlamoq"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar13;